Sirens scream, but I don't hear a thing Clipboards and
contracts they try to bring
Hands reaching out like I'm some kind of case But my answer
's written all over my taste
For sake be meant, here's a paper, your skies Five round of
all, then swallow the mice
D and I need just a gorgeous black BB Don't resuscitate,
don't mess with me, don't
fix me I won't sign your point for a very simple
fee T and I me, T and I me Said debrief, pay lay, bo-oh Now
it runs in this shell
You can chase me down with your answers in meant Ragged
tape and that has just been in
my head Don't call my name like I need to be ditched
Don't write geoc with your metrics enriched You've got your
list and your boss and your
savior plans But it'll burn a day just like where I stand
D and I need just a gorgeous black BB Don't resuscitate,
don't mess with me, don't
fix me I won't sign your point for a very simple
fee T and I need, T and I me Set me free, pray lay, bo-oh
Now it runs in this shell
You can chase me down with your answers in meant Ragged
tape and that has just been in